



Zoran Topić

Nationality: Croatian Date of birth: 16/07/1986 Gender: Male

L Phone number: (+385) 0996395089 **■ Email address:** zoran1607@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zorantopic/

Website: https://www.github.com/morphzg

• Home: Froudeova 1, 10020 Zagreb (Croatia)

ABOUT ME

Ever since a young age, I've had a deep interest in computer science, fueled by my natural curiosity and analytical mindset. While I've pursued a career in the hospitality industry as a waiter, bartender, and barista since 2005, my passion for technology and innovation drives me to new horizons. World of digital technology is where i want to be. From web development to cloud computing and machine learning as my long term goals. Forging a new career path in the dynamic realm of cyberspace.

DIGITAL SKILLS

SQL / Oracle PL/SQL / Python / Linux / HTML / CSS / JavaScript / Github / Git

WORK EXPERIENCE

Coffee bartender

[2005 - Current]

Specialized in coffee preparation and equipment care. Serving.

Graphic designer

Self employed, freelancing [2017 – 2020]

Using most of Adobe suite to offer graphic design services and few video edits. Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro and Aftereffects are tools i was working with.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

CS50 Introduction to computer science

Harvard University online [06/2022 – 10/2022]

Relational Databases

Freecodecamp [10/2022 – 12/2022]

Python Pro Bootcamp

Udemy course; 100 days of code by Angela Yu [04/01/2022 - 10/2022]

Oracle SQL developer

Tonga d.o.o. [02/2023 - 02/2023]

PROJECTS

Open source contributions

Most of my work is stored over github repositories. Available at https://www.github.com/morphzg

Link: https://www.github.com/morphzg

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

From web to machines

Intermediate Python programming, basic SQL and Oracle PL/SQL, Linux shell scripting, HTML, CSS and Markdown. I am analytical and curious by nature, always learning and improving. My long term goals are to become proficient with Python machine learning and data analysis frameworks, cloud computing and web applications.